youzeek.com 2013-06-30

# PRIVACY [] - on YOUZEEK.com

YOUZEEK LLC, a Delaware corporation (YOUZEEK, we or us) aims to create the ultimate music experience.

For this, we need to gather information from you, using your Facebook login. This policy ("YOUZEEK Privacy Policy") describes our online privacy practices and what personal information we may collect from you and what we will and will not do with that information.

* * *

##  How we collect and use personal information

When you sign up for a YOUZEEK account, you will be asked to use your Facebook account to log in. By doing this, you will share basic information from your Facebook account to your YOUZEEK profile. You can find more information about the Facebook privacy policy here: http://www.facebook.com/policy.php  
In addition, when you use the YOUZEEK service, we will automatically collect information about your use of our service such as media you access, queries you make, date and time of your request, your Internet protocol address, performance of your network and computer, your browser type, language and identifying information, your operating system and application version.

We will use your personal information to provide the products and services that you have requested (including the eventual display of customized content and advertising), to communicate with you concerning your account and customer service issues, to ensure the technical functioning of our products and services.

If you are connected with your Facebook profile, you will share your Facebook user name and your Facebook profile picture with your Facebook friend who log in to YOUZEEK with their Facebook account.

Further, the default setting is that all your playlists are visible to your Facebook friends using the YOUZEEK service. If you do not wish for such use of your personal data to take place, you should not connect to YOUZEEK with your Facebook account.

* * *

##  Sharing information with others

YOUZEEK will only share your personal information as is necessary to:

· Provide you with the products or services that you have purchased or requested.

  * Enforce the terms and conditions of the YOUZEEK Terms and Conditions of Use
  * Comply with laws, regulations and any applicable court orders or to respond to or comply with litigation matters or other legal process.
  * Allow advertising audits and analysis measuring the size and composition of the group of users that have listened to and/or viewed an advertisement or other promotional information.

* * *

##  Transfer of personal information to other countries

YOUZEEK processes personal information on servers in a number of countries. We may therefore transfer and process your personal information on a server outside the United States. However, we will use our best efforts to do so in accordance with this YOUZEEK Privacy Policy and applicable law.

* * *

##  Security

We take a number of steps to keep your personal information secure from unauthorized access. For example, we ask you to use a unique and strong password and not to share this information with anyone. In addition, we use encrypted transmissions to limit access to the systems that store your personal information. Further, we respect and comply with applicable laws and regulations on data protection. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your user access name and related password. While we try our best to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

* * *

##  Children´s personal information

The YOUZEEK service is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age you should not use the YOUZEEK Service, and under no circumstances should you provide personal information to us. If we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will immediately delete that child´s information from the YouZeek Service.

* * *

##  Access to personal information and corrections

You can access and update some of the personal information we keep on you through the YOUZEEK Service or by sending a request to privacy@youzeek.com. We will respond to your request upon verification of your identity within a reasonable period of time, and to the maximum extent practical.

* * *

##  Links

We may display links to third party websites. Please note that we cannot control and cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies of such websites. You should always read the privacy policy of a website to find out more about how personal information is collected and processed.

* * *

##  Cookies

We may also store information about you using cookies (files which are sent by us to your computer or other access device) that we can access when you visit the YOUZEEK Websites in future. We do this to help improve the user experience of the website. If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.

* * *

##  Changes to this YOUZEEK Privacy Policy and notices

YOUZEEK reserves the right to make changes to this YOUZEEK Privacy Policy at its sole discretion. If we make any changes to this policy we will notify you by posting the new version of the policy on the YOUZEEK  Websites. It is your own responsibility to check the website for such postings from time to time. You may also be asked to acknowledge one more time and reaccept this Privacy Policy following any material changes.  
Please note that by using the YOUZEEK Service or the YOUZEEK Websites, you consent to the collection and processing of your personal information as described in this YouZeek Privacy Policy, as well as the other terms of this Policy. As mentioned above, we will notify you if we make any changes to this YOUZEEK Privacy Policy by posting the new version of the policy on the YOUZEEK Website. Your continued use of the YOUZEEK Service or the YOUZEEK Website following the posting or other notice of changes to this YOUZEEK Privacy Policy will constitute an acceptance of such changes. If you have any concerns, questions or thoughts on how we can improve our privacy policy, please let us know by sending an email to privacy-feedback@youzeek.com.

* * *

##  Ownership changes

In the event that YOUZEEK or its affiliates, or its or their respective business or this website becomes owned or controlled by other individuals or entities, the information we have collected about you through this website or otherwise may be transferred to such other individuals or entities. In such an event, this Privacy Policy will continue to apply to the information gathered online about you through this site until you are notified otherwise or a change is made to this Policy and posted or notified as provided above.

Copyright ©2011-2013 YOUZEEK LLC. or its affiliates. All rights reserved
